<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fields>
<field>Profile Information
Your Interfold Community Profile will be unlike any other profile on every other social site you have ever discovered.
Built from the ground up literally to let you be in control of the data you'd like to share, however you wish at Any time. In a way that is forever and always truly your own. Prioritizing ideas that you brought to life first in a virtual format.
Welcome to a unique design, where no two profiles will look exactly the same. This is the first of many other input areas you can use, or keep it simple with just one. Whatever you feel best keeps a record of interests of yours, you would like to enjoy with someone else.</field>
<field>Birthday
Add your birthday to your profile.</field>
<field>Gender
Female, Male, X, None
Add your gender to your profile.</field>
<field>Picture
The photo you would like to set as your profile avatar and icon across the site.</field>
<field>Posts
In this part of your profile, you can link to any post that you would like to follow, including your own creations, or otherwise have an interest in contributing to.</field>
<field>Replies
In this part of your profile, you can link to any replies, including your own that you have made on posts you follow.</field>
<field>Embeds
Embed files, or create folders to display media in a design of your choice. With this part of your profile, you can feature items that focus on visual and audio content which can be rendered in any modern internet browser.</field>
<field>Gallery
In this part of your profile, you can link to any media content you follow and make your own gallery of post embeds you find interesting, including items you yourself have added.</field>
<field>Attachments
In this part of your profile, you can control what types of information can be downloaded as a file you have uploaded that other visitors can directly save to their device off site.</field>
<field>Files
In this part of your profile, you can reference files including ones you have posted, as attachments which can be directly saved to your device off site.</field>
<field>Website Address
This part of your profile allows you to add any website address that you would like others to know about, including links to your own profiles on social media or other URLs entirely.</field>
<field>Email Address
This part of your profile lets others contact you directly off site, via email address information you add here.</field>
<field>Telephone Number
This part of your profile allows other visitors to call you, text you or engage with you off site on a live feed.</field>
<field>Friends
Add as many people as you would like to your list of site connections on your profile, where each one tells their own story in relation with yours.</field>
<field>Category
In this part of your profile, you can add categories to help search for terms of interest you follow.</field>
<field>Interests
In this part of your profile, you can add links to categories of interest you follow or contribute to.</field>
<field>Memories
In this part of your profile, you can add memorable dates where important events can, will and are taking place.</field>
<field>Events
In this part of your profile, you can add events with a custom start and finish time for other visitors to add to their schedule alongside your own.</field>
<field>Values
In simple terms, a value is a part of your profile which you can use to add finite numerology with decimal points, for any unit of measurement you are working with.</field>
</fields>
